[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these animals are among the many marine mammals that use songs for the purposes of communication?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Blue Whale", "Humpback whale", "Beluga"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The scapula is part of the spine near the hip.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The title of Kurt Vonneguts book Breakfast of Champions is also the slogan of what famous American breakfast cereal?", "correct_answer": "Wheaties", "incorrect_answers": ["Honey Bunches of Oats", "Krispies", "Cheerios"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "As a child Darth Vader was from what desert planet?", "correct_answer": "Tatooine", "incorrect_answers": ["Alderaan", "Hot", "Endor"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie The Color Purple, what does Miss Celie make and sell to support herself after she leaves Mister?", "correct_answer": "Pants", "incorrect_answers": ["Hats", "Purses", "Cakes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A flatbed scanner enables users to put a text or a computer-generated image on paper or on another medium, such as a transparency.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "George Romeros classic Night of the Living Dead starts with this line.", "correct_answer": "Theyre coming to get you, Barbra!", "incorrect_answers": ["What are you eating, Barbra?", "Theyre dead, Barbra!", "The zombies are here, Barbra!"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When Crash asks Annie (Susan Sarandon) if she has a job in the movie Bull Durham, she said she teaches part time at a local junior college. What subjects does she say she teaches?", "correct_answer": "English 101  Beginning Composition", "incorrect_answers": ["American Literature  Poetry", "Creative Writing  Philosophy", "American  British Literature"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "McConnell Air Force Base is a United States Air Force base located in Sedgwick County, near Wichita, Kansas.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is classified on the Hamilton-Norwood scale?", "correct_answer": "male hair loss", "incorrect_answers": ["fatigue", "blood pressure", "headache"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which actress played Old Rose in the 1997 movie Titanic?", "correct_answer": "Gloria Stuart", "incorrect_answers": ["Kate Winslet", "Gloria Esteban", "Lynn Hollowell"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Winona Ryders character in Alien Resurrection was Callie.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]